- Harry is in hospital ... - mm ...
Dad Axel sleeps with Harry at the hospital.
If you follow our Instagram, you probably already know about this.
We update with pictures and stories daily.
But if you do not, Harry is in hospital.
- Great fever.
- Great fever, exactly.
I dropped like the words.
He has had a fever occasionally for five days.
Great fever, then it went down ...
Very high fever, then it went down.
In fact, when we recorded our last video;
Gingerbread house Challenge ...
... then he had a fever, and then it was gone.
In all cases.
On day five - yesterday, he also began to complain about stomach pain.
Then Axel and I felt that this does not feel good, we take him to the pediatrician.
We come to the pediatrician, they take kissing and some other samples, and say that we have to move on to another doctor.
We move on to another place where they made an ultrasound and saw that his one kidney was swollen.
It was big.
Then we had to move on again.
At Astrid Lindgrens, Harry was hospitalized, and there he remains.
- Mom?
- Yes?
- What is the disease that Harry has?
- It's called renal pelvic inflammation.
Was it hard to get a batter on your stomach?
Yes.
The doctor laid translucent gel on Harry's stomach.
Then she pulled a machine like this to see how the kidneys felt.
- Do you know what she told me, Harry?
- No.
That left kidney is not feeling well.
- But ... now we wait for a ... - should I sleep here again?
We don't know that.
We are waiting for a message if you are allowed to go home, or if you have to stay.
I get sick if I drink all this.
You've been drinking it up now!
Good!
Should you see if you find that drink?
There it is.
The time is now...
Where.
Soon half past six.
This means it's time to pee again.
Okay...
Where!
And then kiss.
- Here at?
- Mm!
Just that, I kissed the poop.
The doctors were in here a little while ago and told me that Harry had to stay another night.
The bacterium that created the urinary tract infection that then went on to the kidneys is an unusual bacterium.
They dare not let him home.
Hello.
Hello friend.
Oh, what you are bad.
Alma, check down!
Right high up ...
Hello Hi, kids!
This is all the way up, what we can go.
- What are you doing?
- Eat french fries and go elevator!
♪ Hey Hops, butt fails!
♪
♪ When the butt comes, every butt should be happy!
You have never been so happy that the children sing about kiss and poop!
I also want to lie down.
He felt so damn crass for a while, but now the energy came back.
Now Alma and Joanna will go home and sleep.
Harry and I are going to get ready and go to bed.
I have ordered a taxi.
It is already nine o'clock.
- I am very tired.
- Me too!
We end today's filming now, we will resume it tomorrow, Harry!
- mm.
Okay, then we say ... "good night" I was saying, we don't say ...
We say;
See you just as soon.
Then it's a new day.
What are you holding up in?
A balloon sword.
He has responded to the treatment, so now his infection value in the blood has gone down.
This means that we may be allowed to go home today!
Yay!
I killed.
What was that clowns?
It was Fjodor and Milda Matilda who knocked on and came in.
They trolled with balls.
- Yes!
- And played with pillows and knotted balloons.
They were great.
Great for him!
Does it hurt, Harry?
No.
Then I pull it out ...
So.
How good you were!
- Cut the hospital band!
- Just that, as you get when you are in hospital.
- Are you prepared, Harry?
- Yes.
Bye.
Oh, nice!
Group hug!
What an emotional carousel this has been ...
- I'm completely exhausted.
- Me too.
Completely finished.
- And grateful!
- Yes!
- That Harry is home!
- It is so nice that he is about to recover again.
- I have such respect for all parents with sick children.
- Yes!
After our short hospital stay, I only know;
God, there are people going through this ...